<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CitiQuiz</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="answer_true"> True </string>
    <string name="answer_false"> False </string>
    <string name="next_question">Next</string>

    <string name="question_pledge"> Francis Bellamy, who composed the pledge in 1892, was a Baptist minister and a socialist. </string>
    <string name="quesiton_flag"> The flag of the United States has 13 stripes to represent the original 13 colonies.</string>
    <string name="question_decl">The Declaration of Independence was not signed on July 4, 1776.</string>
    <string name="question_prcl"> The Emancipation Proclamation ended WWI </string>
    <string name="question_abr">Abraham Lincoln, author of the emancipation, is entombed at the Lincoln Memorial in Washington.</string>
    <string name="question_demo"> The word democracy does not appear in the Constitution. </string>
    <string name="question_quote"> Thomas Jefferson said "Give me liberty or give me death."</string>
    <string name="question_req"> All of the following are requirements to become president of the U.S:

    Must be a natural born U.S. citizen.
    Must be at least 35 years old by the time he/she will serve.
    Must have served at least one term in the Senate.
    Must have lived in the united states for at least 14 years. </string>
    <string name="question_stripes"> There are 50 stripes on the united states flag</string>

    <string name="toast_pledge"> Francis Julius Bellamys pledge The Pledge was published on September 8, 1892 and immediately put to use.</string>
    <string name="toast_flag"> In the end the thirteen colonies were: Delaware, Pennsylvania, New Jersey, Georgia, Connecticut, Massachusetts Bay, Maryland,
        South Carolina, New Hampshire, Virginia, New York, North Carolina, and Rhode Island and Providence Plantations.</string>
    <string name="toast_decl"> Then at war with Great Britain, the 13 colonies regarded themselves as thirteen newly independent sovereign states,
        and no longer a part of the British Empire.</string>
    <string name="toast_prcl"> President Abraham Lincoln issued the Emancipation Proclamation on January 1, 1863, as the nation approached its third year of bloody civil war.
        The proclamation declared "that all persons held as slaves" within the rebellious states "are, and henceforward shall be free."</string>
    <string name="toast_abr"> Lincoln warned the South in his Inaugural Address: "In your hands,
        my dissatisfied fellow countrymen, and not in mine, is the momentous issue of civil war.</string>
    <string name="toast_demo">Democracy definition. A system of government in which power is vested in the
        people, who rule either directly or through freely elected representatives.</string>
    <string name="toast_quote">"Give me liberty, or give me death!" is a quotation attributed
        to Patrick Henry from a speech he made to the Virginia Convention in 1775</string>
    <string name="toast_req">There is no Senate requirement</string>
    <string name="toast_stripes">There are 50 stars on the flag!</string>



</resources>